Mss.B.Sca42
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1609 July 4-1862 January 25; 122.0 folders
  - Subseries C. Jean Robert Poizat letters, 1843 October 27-1860 January 28; 53.0 folders
    - Subsubseries A. Count de Magne of Collége Héraldique de France correspondence with Jean Robert Poizat, 1843 October 27-1847 January 4; 11.0 folders; Count de Magne
      Count de Magne was a member of Collége Héraldique de France and all of the letters are written on its letterhead. This correspondence records Jean Robert Poizat's attempts to have the College of Heralds recognize his relation to the Scaliger family. There are a few letters within this collection from the Marquis de Magne, Collége Héraldique et Archéologisque de France but the members of the board are almost the same as that of the Collége Héraldique de France and the letterhead is similar so it is most likely the same person or closely connected to the Count de Magne.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1843 October 27; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1843 November 8; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1843 November 27; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1844 January 10; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1844 February 21; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1844 May 13; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1844 June 27; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1845 July 21; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1845 August 13; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Count de Magne, 1845 October 13; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from the Marquis de Magne, 1847 January 4; 1.0 item; Count de Magne (Box 2, Folder 11)
        This letter is from the Marquis de Magnne, Collége Héraldique et Archéologisque de France but the board listed on the letterhead is nearly identicle to that of the Comte de Magne at the Collége Héraldique de France so they are probably the same person or closely connected.
    - Letter to Monsieur J. Poisat, 1846 December 15; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 12)
      While this letter is addressed to Jean Robert Poizat, it is unclear who it is from.
    - Subsubseries B. Alexandre Froyez correspondence with Jean Robert Poizat, 1847 January 30-1850 July 18; 6.0 folders; Froyez, Alexandre
      Alexandre Froyez was a lawyer who Jean Robert Poizat had a correspondence with from 1847 to 1850.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Alexandre Froyez, circa 1847-1850; 1.0 item; Froyez, Alexandre (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Alexandre Froyez, 1847 January 30; 5.0 items; Froyez, Alexandre (Box 2, Folder 14)
        This folder contains the business card of Alexandre Froyez, an envelope and three separate sheets of paper
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Alexandre Froyez, 1847 February 26; 2.0 items; Froyez, Alexandre (Box 2, Folder 15)
        This folder contains both an envelope and a letter
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Alexandre Froyez, 1847 August 8; 1.0 item; Froyez, Alexandre (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Alexandre Froyez, 1848 February 11; 2.0 items; Froyez, Alexandre (Box 2, Folder 17)
        This folder contains two copies of the same letter. One written in Froyez' handwriting and another copy of the same letter but in a different handwriting.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Alexandre Froyez, 1850 July 18; 2.0 items; Froyez, Alexandre (Box 2, Folder 18)
        An envelope is included with the letter in this folder.
    - Subsubseries C. Victoire de Vérone correspondence with Jean Robert Poizat, 1847 March-1852 July 8; 31.0 folders; Vérone, Victoire de
      These letters passed between Victoire de Vérone, the last true Scaliger, and Jean Robert Poizat of the illegitimate branch of the family from Santo Domingo. They record the transfer of documents relating to the family lineage to the Poizats and Victoire de Vérone's appeals for financial aid.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, undated; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 March; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 March 4; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 April 19; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 22)
        This folder contains both a letter and its original envelope.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 May 21; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 June 9; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 August 21; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 25)
        There is an envelope included with the letter in this folder.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 August 27; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 September 14; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 September 16; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 September 18; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 November 9; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 November 26; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1847 December 9; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 January; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 February 15; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 March 3; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 March 26; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 April 17; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 May 16; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 May 18; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 August 23; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 41)
        This folder includes the original envelope for the letter.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1848 September 27; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1849 April 14; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 43)
        The letter in this folder is included with its original envelope.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1849 August 1; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 44)
        The original envelope is included with the letter in this folder.
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1850 February 12; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1850 June 20; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1851 April 18; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1852 January 26; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Letter to Jean Robert Poizat from Victoire Scaliger de Verone, 1852 July 8; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Letter to Monseiur le Comte de Salvandy from Victoire Scaliger de Verone on behalf of Jean Robert Poizat, 1848; 1.0 item; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Demande d'addition de nom Poizat de Lescale de Verone a son excellence le Garde des Sceaus Ministre sécretaire d'Etat, au Department de la Justice, 1848 February; 1.0 item; Poizat, Jean Robert, 1803-1868 July 18 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Letter to Mon Cher Poizat, 1853 April 12; 2.0 items; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 52)
      Within this letter there is an enclosed letter from Victoire Scaliger de Verone
    - Letter to Monsieur Poizat from Capt Morhaine Monseigneur le Comte de Paris, 1860 January 28; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 53)
      There is both the original envelope and the letter within this folder
  - Letter to Victoire Scaliger de Veronne from Marquis de Magne, 1847 January 27; 1.0 item; Count de Magne; Vérone, Victoire de (Box 2, Folder 54)
    This letter is from the Marquis de Magne, Collége Héraldique et Archéologisque de France but the board listed on the letterhead is nearly identicle to that of the Comte de Magne at the Collége Héraldique de France so they are probably the same person or closely connected.
  - Letter to Monseigneur le Comte de Paris Prince, 1862 January 25; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Series II. Genealogical material, 36.0 folders
  - Bazzoni family- family tree, after 1769; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Bazzoni
  - Bousquet family- collection of notes, after 1893; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 2)
    Bousquet
  - Doutes sur les dattes, after 1657; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Drawing of a man, undated; 1.0 Drawing (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Family crest drawing I, undated; 1.0 Drawing (Box Oversize 1)
  - Family crest drawing II, after 1421; 1.0 Drawing (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Family crest drawing III, after 1661; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Greek verses and their translations used by Jules Caeser, undated; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    Scaliger, Julius Caesar, 1484-1558
  - Greek verses, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Inventory of the Poizat collection, 1900 June; 3.0 items (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Poizat
  - Mémoires ecrites par Joseph Scaliger- notes, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Although this document is undated, it is written on one sheet of a more modern-looking white lined paper.
  - Monmejan family- family tree I, after 1689; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Monmejan
  - Monmejan family- family tree II, after 1711 April 11; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 5)
  - Monmejan family- family tree III, after 1711; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 6)
  - Monmejan family- notes on the Monmejan and St. André branches of the family, 1778; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Montault family- continuation de la généalogie de Monsieur le Comte de Montault, after 1665; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    The full title reads, "continuation de la généalogie de Monsieur le Comte de Montault pour servir de suite a celle qui a été commencée par M. de Beaujon généalogiste de ordres du roy"
    This document can be found in OVersize Box 1.
  - Montault family- escusson et armories, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 11)
    The full title reads, "escusson et armories de mepire Francois Michel de St Cevier Montault seigneur du ma lartie, la deillau, le sounon et autres places"
  - Montault family- family tree, after 1657; 2.0 items (Box Oversize 1, Folder 8)
  - Montault family- genealogical tree of the house of Montault St. Siver, after 1720; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 9)
  - Montault family- genealogy of the Montault St. Siviers since 1300, after 1750; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 1, Folder 10)
  - Note des cretes a chercher, after 1669; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Note on titles, after 1755; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Lescale de Vérone, Julius Caesar de, -1726
  - Numbered notes, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pieces trouvees dans le premier coffre, 1694 October 28; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Scaliger family- genealogical notes and family crests of the Scaliger and Montault families, after 1711; 6.0 items (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Montault; Scaliger
  - Scaliger family- genealogy of the de Lescale de Verone family, before 1667 February 18; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 17)
    A note on the back of the document reads, "geneologie des messieurs de lescale de veronne produite le 18 fevrier 1667 devant Mr. de pelot commissaire..."
  - Scaliger family- genealogy of the Scaliger Family of Verona and the Poizat family, after 1790; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Poizat; Scaliger
  - Scaliger family- inventory of the Scaliger family genealogy, 1690 August 5; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 19)
    This document was presented to the court by Joseph Lescale de Vérone.
  - Scaliger family- liste des portraits de la famille Scaliger de Verone, after 1809; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Scaliger family- list of Scaliger family legal documents and notes, after 1614 July 1; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Scaliger family- notes 1, undated; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 22)
    See also, "Scaliger family- Scropius", "Scaliger family- notes 2", and "Scaliger family- notes 3"
    This item consists of several pages of notes filled with edits, notes in the margins, and notations crossed. Julius Caesar Scaliger's name appears several times as well as the word "scropius," and there are notes about the princes of Verona. A note originally attached to the folder reads "Doc-- J.C.S. (illegible words)." The note is included in with the document.
    Scaliger, Julius Caesar, 1484-1558; Scaliger
  - Scaliger family- notes 2, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 23)
    See also, "Scaliger family- notes 1" and "Scaliger family- notes 3"
    This document has a similar handwriting to that seen on "Scaliger family- notes 1" albiet messier. This document also has notes in the margins and items crossed out. More legible sections of the document mention members of the Scaliger family, "l'origine des Scaligers," and the princes of Verone.
  - Scaliger family- notes 3, after 1595; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 24)
    See also, "Scaliger family- notes 1" and "Scaliger family- notes 2"
    This document is also written in a similar handwriting to Scaliger family notes 1 and 2. It too mentions members of the Scaliger family and the della Scallas.
  - Scaliger family- notes on the relationship between the Scaliger Family and the Princes of Verone, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Scaliger family- Scropius, after 1519; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 26)
    See also, "Scaliger family-notes"
    Card clipped to the front of the original forlder reads, "Abrege de Maison de Scala of Verona-- no mention of (illegible word) of Agen"
  - Trouve pieces atacheés ensemble- note, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    This is an informal note that was presumably attached to several documents.
- Series III. Works by Scaliger family members, 14.0 folders
  - Abregé, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box Oversize 1, Folder 11)
    The full title is "Abregé de l'histoire de la masion d'ella Scala ou Scaligers princes de Véronne et de sa decadeance"
  - Abbregé de l'histoire de la maison des Scaligers princes de Verone et de la decadance, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Card attached to the original file reads "DR-J.C.S." in the author column
  - Abregé- continued, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 2)
    A note clipped to the front of the original folder reads "J.C.S. Cont of Abregé"
  - Ces ecussons vous ferons connaitres des familles avec qui nous sommes allieés, after 1781; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dissertation historique et critique sur l'origin de Jules Caesar Scaliger, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dissertation historique et critique sur l'origine de Jules Caesar Scaliger, undated; 1.0 item; The full title is difficult to read but a partial transcription could be "Dissertation historique et critique sur l'origine de Jules Caesar Scaliger ou l'on fait voir comment a été inventée la fable des burdons avec le...qui la composée." This document is wrapped in a more modern piece of white lined paper with "No. 5" written on it.; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Eclaircillement de la fable des burdons ou dissertation historique sur l'origine de Jules Caesar Scaliger, undated; 2.0 items; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 6)
    The full title is "Eclaircillement de la fable des burdons ou dissertation historique sur l'origine de Jules Caesar Scaliger pour servir de rêsponse a une lettre êcrit a l'autheur de la precedente histoire." This document is wrapped in a more modern-looking piece of white lined paper with "No. 4" written on it.
  - Memoires de la maison des Scaligers escrits par Joseph Scaliger, undated; 1.0 item; Charrier de Lescale de Vérone, Joseph de, -1689 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    The full title reads, "Memoires de la maison des Scaligers escrits par Joseph Scaliger hoir, heritier, et chef du nom et armes de cette maison donnés a Jeane Anthoinete de Lescale de Verone fille aisnée de l'autheur"
    Lescale de Vérone, Jeane Anthoinete de; Scaliger
  - Memoires de la maison des Scaligers escrits par Joseph Scaliger- partial transcription, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 8)
    The full title reads, "Memoires de la maison des Scaligers escrits par Joseph Scaliger hoir, heritier, et chef du nom et armes de cette maison donnés a Jeane Anthoinete de Lescale de Verone fille aisnée de l'autheur" but this only represents a partial transcription written on what seems to be more modern paper.
    Charrier de Lescale de Vérone, Joseph de, -1689; Lescale de Vérone, Jeane Anthoinete de; Scaliger
  - Memoires sur l'origine de Jules Caesar Scaliger, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 9)
    This manuscript is written on larger paper with a copious amount of notes in the margins
  - Memoires sur l'origine de Jules Caesar Scaliger, undated; 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 10)
    This manuscript is written on smaller paper with fewer notes in the margins. The card attached to the original file reads "18th cent? de J.C. Scaliger
  - Memoire sur la genealogie des Scaligers année 1791 section 1, 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Scaliger; Unidentified
  - Memoires of Scaliger- beginning, after 1539; 2.0 items; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 12)
    A note on the front of the original folder reads, "Beginning of Mem of Scaliger 56 pp." Enclosed are two packets of paper wrapped in a more modern-looking lined paper labeled No 2 and No 3.
    Scaliger, Joseph Juste, 1540-1609; Scaliger, Julius Caesar, 1484-1558; Scaliger
  - Me moyra des naissances de nos enfans de l'an 1623, 1.0 item; Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Series IV. Military, legal,and financial documents, 1459-1847 October 22; 142.0 folders
  - Document, 1459; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    This document is one large square of parchment with text written on it. There is a drawing, perhaps a family insignia at the bottom along with a short sentance or two written in a different colored ink as the rest of the text.
    This document can be found in Oversize Box 2.
  - Document about a fief, 1476 April 22; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 4, Folder 1)
    This document is one large square of parchment with text written on it. There is a drawing, perhaps a family insignia at the bottom along with a short sentance or two written in a different colored ink as the rest of the text. The word fief is mentioned in a note on the back of the document.
    This document can be found in Oversize Box 4.
  - Document about a fief, 1483; 1.0 item (Oversize Map Room, Folder 1)
    This item can be found in the Scaliger Family Papers drawer in the Map Room in the Subbasement.
    This is a large rectangular shaped piece of parchment with three drawings at the bottom, which could be family insignias. There is a note on the back that also includes the word fief.
  - Document about a fief, 1488 February 17; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    The handwriting used on this document is difficult to read making it hard to discern what kind of document it is but a fief is mentioned in a note on the back of the document.
  - Document about a fief, 1492; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    This is a square of parchment with three drawings at the bottom, which could be family insignias. There is a note on the back that also includes the word fief.
  - Document, 1492 January 24; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 4, Folder 2)
    This document is one large rectangle of parchment with three drawings at the bottom, which could be family insignias.
  - Document, 1494; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 4, Folder 3)
    This document is one large square of parchment with a small drawing at the bottom.
  - Document, 1500; 1.0 item (Oversize Map Room, Folder 2)
    The name Jacob Montault appears to be written on the back of this document. It is a large rectangular sheet of parchment with drawings at the bottom that could be family insignias.
  - Document, 1500 April 24; 1.0 item (Oversize Map Room, Folder 3)
    This is a rectangular sheet of parchment with drawings at the bottom that could be family insignias.
  - Document, 1509; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    This is a large square of parchment with three drawings at the bottom that could be family insignias. Some of the text is underlined in a different ink color.
  - Insteament vieil appartenant, 1522 April 24; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 4, Folder 4)
    This document is one large rectange of parchment with a small drawing at the bottom. There is a note on the back, which is difficult to read but looks to begin with the words, "insteament vieil appartenant."
  - Document about a fief, 1524 January 27; 1.0 item (Box Oversize 4, Folder 5)
    This document is one large rectangle of parchment with text written on it. There is a drawing, perhaps a family insignia. The word fief is mentioned in a note on the back of the document.
  - Letre de naturalite, 1528 March; 1.0 item (Box Seal)
    This document can be found in the box "Documents with seals to go to Conservation." Be careful because these documents have yet to be put in suitable containers to preserve the seals.
    Be careful this document still has the original seal attached. Julius Caesar Scaliger became a French citizen in 1528 so this could be the document acknowledging his naturalization.
  - Scaliger, Julius Caesar- exchange, 1529 April 15; 1.0 item (Oversize Map Room, Folder 4)
    This document was found in the same original folder as "Sachent tous" dated 1607 December, "Charrier de Lescale de Vérone, Joseph de- document" dated 1529 April 15, and "Arrest" dated 1672 May 21.
  - Scaliger, Julius Caesar- document, 153-; 1.0 item (Box Seal)